Summary

I am a highly motivated individual with nearly 2 years of software development experience. I see programming as fun rather than work and am eager to leverage my solid development skills, with a focus on collaboration, communication, passion and creativity, as a programmer. My ultimate goal is to devise a better problem-solving method for challenging tasks, and to continuously learn new technologies and tools. I am excited to join a team where I can contribute my skills, learn from my colleagues and make a positive impact on the projects I work on, all while continuing to enjoy the process of programming.

Skills

Front-end React, Next.js, Redux, Tailwind CSS, Material UI, Cypress, Jest, Framer Motion

Back-end Node.js, FastAPI

Programming JavaScript, Java, Python, Sql, NoSql, REST API, Docker, Linux commands, Firebase, MongoDB Git, Gerrit, LaTeX, Scrum

Languages English, Hungarian

Interests Coding, Photoshop, Running, Playing board games with friends

Work Experience

Cloudera Budapest

SOFTWARE ENGINEER INTERN

• Close cooperation with the UX designers

- · Design implementation using React and Typescript which improved the site usability
- Led the redesign and enhancement of features by utilizing a combination of personal and team-generated ideas resulting in a refined user experience
- Test coverage increased by 30% with Cypress and Jest
- The speed of the page load increased by 27%
- · Played a crucial role in creating a new endpoint, utilizing open-source Kafka technology as part of the Kafka team

Evosoft Budapest

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER INTERN Marc, 2022 - Jun, 2022

- Develop and maintain a UI for automated production lines
- · Analysis and design of the login page requirements in collaboration with the architect
- Promoting the introduction and adoption of clean code principles

Eötvös Loránd University

Budapest

ALGORITHMS AND DATA STRUCTURES I. TUTOR

Feb. 2022 - Jun. 2022

- Instructed a group of 20 students on the fundamentals of algorithms and data structures.
- Provided examples of both simple and complex algorithms to the students.

EricssonBudapest

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER INTERN

Jul. 2021 - jan. 2022

· Created a debugging tool using shellscript that utilizes Wireshark and integrates with Kubernetes to inject the tool into containers.

Education

Eötvös Loránd University

Budapest

M.A. IN COMPUTER SCIENCE Sep. 2022 - Jun. 2024

Eötvös Loránd University

Budapest

B.S. IN COMPUTER SCIENCE Sep. 2019 - Jun. 2022

Side projects

Pathfinging visualizer

THESIS WORK

- A fullstack application that shows the user how the pathfinding algorithms work
- The user interface was built with React and Tailwind CSS, tested with Cypress
- The backend is built using Python FastAPI
- I was able to learn about various advanced pathfinding algorithms and understand how they work like Dijkstra, A*, D*

Booking

PERSONAL PROJECT

- Developed a full-stack application that allows users to make reservations for holidays.
- Developed the user interface for the application using **React**, **Tailwind CSS** and **Redux**
- I built the backend of the application using **Node.js** and the database was **MongoDB**

Portfolio

PERSONAL PROJECT

- I have built my portfolio using a design from Figma
- The front-end was constructed using Next.js 13 and Tailwind CSS
- The animations were handled with the sophisticated **Framer Motion**

Wedding

PERSONAL PROJECT

- Designed and built a user interface that allowed me to improve my skills in user experience design and CSS.
- The UX design was made with Figma the UI with React Tailwind CSS
- The animations were handled with the sophisticated **Framer Motion**.

Amazon warehouse simulation

UNIVERSITY GROUP PROJECT

- A team project where a warehouse had to be simulated with automated robots
- The software was written in C# following the MVVM architecture, of which I was mainly responsible for the model layer.